HIKARI KOBE Front-End Developer -

(778)840-1785 | Marie h.kobe712@gmail.com | Vancouver, BC | Hikari7 | Portfolio | In hikari-kobe

SUMMARY

As a specialized Front-End Developer with expertise in React, I am dedicated to creating user-friendly websites utilizing my proficiency in CSS, JavaScript, and React. With 3 years of experience as a technical support specialist in customer service, I possess exceptional communication skills and the ability to collaborate effectively with team members. Seeking a position in a team environment to further hone my skills as a Front-End Developer.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks, Libraries, and Environments: React, Redux, React Router, Sass, Bootstrap,

Material UI, Styled-component, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Express, Gatsby, Node.js

Others: Firebase, MongoDB, Git, Figma

PROJECTS

Workout Tracker (React, Material UI, Firebase)

A workout tracker recording app provides the store the user information and their posts. Manipulating data with Firebase.

Sleep tight (React, GSAP, Tailwind CSS, Youtube Data API v3)

A web app only plays BGM-related relaxing sounds fetched by Youtube Data API. Well designed the minimized styling to help the user to focus on sleeping.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer/Desginer (Freelance) | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

Whistleblowing Software

Developed a secure platform for anonymous reporting of issues

Designed and implemented the front-end of the software

Second-hand Book E-commerce Site

Collaborated with a startup company based in Nigeria to deliver the project

- Contributed to the design and development of the site as a front-end Developer
- Improved user experience and aesthetic appeal of the site by working on the front-end

Technical Support Specialist / Trainer, Japan Concentrix k.k | Japan | 2019.4 - 2022.2

- Offered various customer technical support ranging from supporting the launch of a hotel property's website on the online travel agency site and to game player technical support.
- Trained more than 130 employees successfully and received the Best Employee of the Quarter Award for my training achievements.

EDUCATION

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

Web and Mobile Application Development Diploma

Seinan Gakuin University | Japan | 2014.4 - 2018.3

Bachelor of Intercultural studies